

# **FAROUK BENDEROUICHE**

Address: Bizerte zarouna 613, Tunis

**Phone:** +216 55 304 138

Email: faroukbdr963@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

I'am a student at the University of Sciences of Bizerte and a graduate with a Bachelor's degree in Software Engineering, specializing in Information Systems and now currently im student at Esprit For my engineering degree. In addition to my university studies, I am strongly committed to independent learning and recognize that the Internet is an invaluable tool for personal and professional development. I have actively developed my skills through several online courses, including Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA), the Harvard CS50 course with Django, a selection of courses on platforms such as edX, Codecademy, and other learning resources.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Web Developer, Tunisise Telecom

Jul 2023 - Aug 2023

- I designed and developed a website to calculate the profitability of the radio network sites
- my internship experience at Tunisie Telecom taught me a valuable lesson about teamwork.
- By closely collaborating with colleagues from diverse backgrounds, I gained a deep understanding of the importance of collaboration

#### Al Developer, Symolia

Feb 2024 - jun 2024

- I worked with SpaCy,a powerful tool for natural language processing
- My primary role was to train Al models by annotating data for a project involving CV and job offer parsing, as well as CV/job matching.
- allowed me to develop practical skills inartificial intelligence and contribute meaningfully to the company's projects.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Software Engineering Computer Science with Honors**

Faculty of Sciences of Bizerte

Sep 2021 - Jun 2024

- Conducted comprehensive research on the latest advancements in software engineering technologies and methodologies.
- Developed innovative software solutions that enhance system efficiency and performance.

### **Baccalaureate in Technology**

Sep 2019 - Jun 2020

College Bech Hanba

- · Specialized in mechanics and electronics.
- Acquired a strong foundation in technical principles and practical skills related to mechanical and electronic systems.

## **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

- **Technical Skills:** Java, Javascript, Python: Django, Flask, Web Design, React, Machine Learning, Project Management, Databases, Networking, Web Development, Artificial Intelegence
- Languages: Arabic, English, German, French.
- Formation: cs50 ,leetcode, Randotek react, codeacademy, Cisco